Hello hello everyone today we have introduced a reminder for you from Bajay
General Insurance Company
which will be
added in the name of Help Rider this is an OPD benefit
rider which you
can do both and this side has very
good features and it is available at a very reasonable
price
you can buy a rider for yourself by spending less than the normal one you can
find out how much it costs
if you want complete information then
watch this video completely before starting the video
I want to tell you my
name is and I am associated with this industry for the last 12
years on this channel we
share information regarding insurance and investment if you
want to keep yourself updated then do subscribe to our channel you
can take this remedy for both individual and family floater
we are putting a list of the products in which you can add this rider on the screen
which you can check you can do this in their
health insurance policy and Pi Nikli
Rochelle accident policy this
company has introduced approx
90 doctors have been contacted all over India, through
which
subscribe and
subscribe the channel company has contacted
and both the benefits can be availed.
Talking about subscription,
if the policy holder is travelling due to any disease, the
policy holder can
consult the doctor for unlimited time, which can be done through
audio video chat,
which is done through
contact. The second benefit is
doctor consultation cover, if the policy holder does
not want to consult online and
goes for physical consultation, then in this policy,
whichever doctor is available in their network hospital with
which there is a tie-up, the
policy holder can get his treatment done from there,
if he consults any doctor, then you
can click on it. Whatever is limited in that too, whichever policy holder
decides,
you can click there.
In the third benefit, investigation cover
covers radiologic arrest, there is increase in saliva,
ultrasound extra, if you
require interest for treatment, then you
can get your tests done through this and whatever your
limit is, the claim is up to that limit.  You can do
all your medical
diagnostic tests in pathology like return and blood
relatives etc., so whatever this
requirement is, it can be cleared in this policy.
Benefits Rider Meghwal
Preventive
Subscription is available in every option, if
you take individual then you get it
and if you take family floater plan
then you get two coupons, you can subscribe five in it,
from there you can get your tests done, you
can click for the expenses of subscription investigation pathology and radiology, whereas
in the option file you can subscribe doctor consultation power of 300 and
investigation cover for pathology and radiology,
three
options are available in Ramesh which I am putting on the screen,
you can check, in this option there is
doctor consultation cover up to 25 thousand rupees and
investigation more and for this you can click, if you
decide then
you will have to follow the eligibility criteria in it
and you can subscribe to this, if you subscribe then
you have to wait for 30 days  Subscribe to the period, it
cannot be cleared before thirty days. The
account from which it is available in Sider is available.
If you take a policy for family size tumor,
tempered glass discount, then you
can subscribe,
but in this you have to keep in mind that if
you commit suicide, then you will
not get the online subscription.
Subscribe. The
subscription is done by the company, which is very much, you
can see on this screen, for this
you can get it for yourself by subscribing. When you
can cover the school, that Bajaj Alliance has
added a very good reminder, which
you can add with these existing policies, you
can do it with the Friends policy,
that it is available in a very reasonable price,
so all this information is
about the General Insurance Company,
if you liked the video, then we keep
bringing information, so please
like our channel and subscribe, thank
you for watching.